Guide to the H.H. Walker, Signature Album
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
[Signature album]
1870-1870
OSBORN D65
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
0.13
(1 volume)
Autograph MSS. Collection of signatures, mostly cut, and a few letters of British bishops, peers, and members of the Royal family; some signatures accompanied with photographs of authors.
Walker, H. H.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
For provenance information, consult the appropriate curator.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
The following finding aid is a partial inventory of the contents of Osborn d65. This list was reformatted from previously existing cataloging.
Autographs -- Great Britain; Walker, H. H.
- Osborn d65
  - ELLICOTT, CHARLES JOHN, BP. OF GLOUCESTER, 1819-1905
    - ALS to unnamed recipient, [no yr] Nov 12 (Box 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Gloucester
      1 p.; 18 x 11 cm.
      Sends his autograph with advice to
      the recipient: " Public men are
      often good-natured, but always busy
      send then with your applications a
      directed envelope in each case."
      d.65/100
  - LYVEDEN, ROBERT VERNON, 1ST BARON, 1800-1873
    - ALS to an unidentified recipient, 1870 Jun 29 (Box 1)
      n.p. 1 p.; 18 x 11 cm. d.65/73
  - TEMPLE, FREDERICK, ABP. OF CANTERBURY, 1821-1902
    - ALS to Mr. Wolfe, 1870 Dec 23 (Box 1)
      Exeter
      3 p.; 18 x 11 cm.
      Accompanied by a photograph of
      Temple.
      d.65/97
  - TYNDALL, JOHN, 1820-1893
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, [no yr] May 4 (Box 1)
      Royal Institution
      d.65/128
  - WORDSWORTH, CHRISTOPHER, BP. OF LINCOLN, 1807-1885
    - ALS to an unnamed recipient, 1872 Nov 11 (Box 1)
      Lincoln
      2 p.; 14 x 9 cm.
      Thanks for a letter.
      d.65/120